{
    "id": "8d214dd42c9644b39dfb7bc731dfa32c",
    "title": "Gap Fills Exercise",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "Susie ……………………….. a new boyfriend.",
            "description": "Either could be used here. However, the got form of have is more common.",
            "answers": [
                "has",
                "has got",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "fc1fe29280a646d0b5f8cb7ba88b6126"
        },
        {
            "question": "I ……………………….. fever last week.",
            "description": "Got forms are not common with had.",
            "answers": [
                "had",
                "had got",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "755780d985ef4cf69600e5bd35f776aa"
        },
        {
            "question": "…………………………… good neighbors when you lived in the city?",
            "description": "Got forms are not common with had.",
            "answers": [
                "Had you got",
                "Did you have",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "e2ac7b29a1f842d99aa65b1a42e0b578"
        },
        {
            "question": "I ………………………….. a toothache.",
            "description": "Progressive forms of have are not normally used with meanings that refer to a state.",
            "answers": [
                "have got",
                "have",
                "am having"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "81a39484d05e41a58c64ed1ffeee77de"
        },
        {
            "question": "You ………………………….. to work on Sundays.",
            "description": "In negative sentences we use do not have.",
            "answers": [
                "haven't",
                "don't have",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "3f07e37e9f044ab29a3aae5b9a2193b1"
        },
        {
            "question": "Suddenly I ………………………. a thud.",
            "description": "We use listen to to talk about paying attention to sounds that are going on.",
            "answers": [
                "heard",
                "listened to",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "cbd1b742a2de44ca95bb7de72555fd05"
        },
        {
            "question": "Can you help me ……………………….. my ring?",
            "description": "The infinitive can be used with or without to after help.",
            "answers": [
                "find",
                "to find",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "df004bf0a094488d8856133feeebae30"
        },
        {
            "question": "How ………………………. is she?",
            "description": "We use tall for people, trees, buildings etc.",
            "answers": [
                "tall",
                "high",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "23be7a7ecf1c40b38aa696b1d131892b"
        },
        {
            "question": "You have got lovely ………………………… legs.",
            "description": "Parts of the body can be long, not tall.",
            "answers": [
                "tall",
                "long",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "0256197b857646e3b27792684c00f8e4"
        },
        {
            "question": "How …………………………. Sundays!",
            "description": "The verb comes after the subject in exclamations.",
            "answers": [
                "I love",
                "do I love"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "c02e606852e444098a74e15011a68827"
        },
        {
            "question": "How ……………………….. grown!",
            "description": "The verb comes after the subject in exclamations.",
            "answers": [
                "have you",
                "you have",
                "do you have"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "e2a5f94a471542b7863ce072846b9003"
        },
        {
            "question": "Stir well ………………………. I do.",
            "description": "In comparisons we use as, like or the way. We don’t use how.",
            "answers": [
                "as",
                "like",
                "the way",
                "how"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "341a3288088f49898cf038478509bada"
        }
    ]
}